

# CONTACT



hmdarden97@gmail.com

+1 (479) 329-8640

# **EDUCATION**

 UNIVERSITY OF ARKANSAS AT LITTLE ROCK

WEB DESIGN & DEVELOPMENT - BA
IN PROGRESS- EXPECTED MAY, 2024

GOOGLE- COURSERA

PROJECT MANAGEMENT- CERTIFICATE
IN PROGRESS- EXPECTED MAY, 2024

# **SKILLS**

HTML/CSS

JAVASCRIPT

GIT/GITHUB

WORDPRESS

FIGMA

**ELEMENTOR** 

ADOBE CREATIVE CLOUD

# **SOCIALS**









# Hannah M. Darden

Web Developer

### **PROFILE**

Current Senior at the University of Arkansas at Little Rock pursing a BA in Web Design and Development, minoring in Information Technology. Diverse experience in HTML/CSS, design, client-customer management and training, computer multitasking, and problem solving. strong interest and growing skillset in UX/UI design and project management.

## **INTERNSHIP**

Summer 2023

#### **HELP ASSISTANT**

**EMERGING ANALYTICS CENTER- UALR** 

Worked on projects for the Art and Web Development teams. Assisted in the creation and maintenance of sites hosted through the center. Received training in new tools and softwares such as Confluence, Blender, and 3Ds Max. Furthered my skillset in sites such as Wordpress and SiteGround.

# WORK EXPERIENCE

2023-Present

#### **CENTRALIZED STAFFING COORDINATOR**

**BAPTIST HEALTH** 

Multitasking which included daily medical staffing for multiple locations. Responded to employee questions regarding schedules, timekeeping, and daily staffing.

2019-2023

#### **EMERGENCY COMMUNICATIONS DISPATCHER**

**BRYANT COMMUNICATIONS** 

Multitasking which included documentation entry while radio, phone, and camera monitoring. Dispatched for fire, medical rescue, and police. Trained new dispatchers to ensure efficient communication and response times.

2018 – 2019

## PHARMACY TECHNICIAN/FLOATER

CVS

Entered and filled patient prescriptions. Took calls and made calls to patients, doctors, and insurance companies. Engagement and enhancing customer experience. Responding to customers requests as needed. Orchestrated exemplary services by greeting customers courteously and offering assistance when needed

#### REFERENCES

**LEE ANN CLEGHORN** 

CITY OF BRYANT

PHONE: 501-860-5191

**SETH WAKEFIELD** 

CITY OF BRYANT

**PHONE:** 501-256-4129

**TAYA COVEY** 

CITY OF BRYANT

**PHONE:** 501-860-8043